早上好
Hey.
慢点  小美人
Slow down, sister.
事实上  我得快点
Actually, I need to speed up.
瑞秋一大早起来就发烧
Rachel woke up early with a fever
已经让我担惊受怕了一早上
And she's been terrorizing me all morning.
我已经迟到了
I'm already late.
对不起  监视工作比我想象的要长
Sorry, stakeout went longer than I thought.
你怪我吗
Have you ever been to a rave?
再见
Good-bye.
你已经迟到了  瑞秋也病了
You're already late and Rachel's sick.
即使现在走  也无济于事
Neither of which can be solved by you leaving
享受当下吧 整个医院都等我完成悬而未决的议案呢
Right this second. The entire hospital is depending on a proposal I've yet to finish
必须8点30前提出来
And need to present at 8:30.
现在才七点半
It`s 7:30.
已经7点37了
It`s 7:37.
我让你10分钟就到医院
I'll have you on the road in ten minutes.
你不想总因为开会紧张兮兮的吧
Come on, you don't want to go into your meeting all tight
压得你喘不过气来  不是吗
And stressed out, do you?
-你电话响了  -是豪斯  别理他
- That's yours. - It's house. Ignore it.
上面写着"紧急事件"
It says "Emergency page."
我说别理他
I said ignore it.
亲爱的
Sweet.
对不起
I'm sorry.
总想着要时间长点
It's hard to pace yourself
反而立马缴械投降了
When you've been thinking about it for ten hours straight.
太棒了  现在我既迟到了
That's great. Now I'm late,
又紧张  而且受打击
Stressed out, and frustrated.
对不起
Sorry.
如果再给我一分钟  我会...
If you give me a minute, I can...
下次吧
It'll wait.
你行的
You can do it.
行什么
Do what?
我以为你7点30就能来呢
I thought you were coming in at 7:30.
瑞秋早上起来发烧了
Rachel woke up with a fever
所以我  就来的晚了
And then I...just couldn't get here any sooner.
药房里有点麻烦
There's a problem in the pharmacy.
你好  老大
Hey, boss lady!
你连紧急呼叫都不回么
You don't answer emergency pages anymore?
跟他们说我会尽快到场
Tell them all I'll be by as soon as I can
跟他说我肯定这次不是狼来了
And tell him I assumed it was either about the wolf again
也不少昨天那个手续我不批
Or the procedure I refused to approve yesterday.
结果却不是抗药性金黄色葡萄球菌感染
Turned out it wasn't a resistant staph,
但我还是说  如果是的话
But I still say that if it had been,
应该给他感染疟疾病毒
Infecting him with malaria...
说真的  豪斯  我没时间理这个
Seriously, house, I don't have time for this.
-你撒谎  -还有20分钟开会
- You're lying. - I have a meeting in 20 minutes.
说的不是你的会议
Not talking about your meeting.
我说的是电话
I'm talking about the phone call.
我没问你说的是什么
I didn't ask what you were talking about,
因为我不在乎
Because I don't care.
我昨晚和你宝贝儿一起监视了
I was with your boy toy on a stakeout last night.
你昨晚和卢卡斯在一起吗
You were with lucas?
他需要有人
He needed someone who could diagnose
给他诊断一下软组织损伤
A soft tissue injury from across the street.
显然他不认识什么好医生
Apparently he doesn't know any good doctors.
或者他认识的那个 工作之余根本没空
Or the ones he does know actually have lives outside of work.
监视工作不太忙
Things got a little slow,
所以我们打了个赌
So we made some wagers.
打赌我能不能
One being whether I could get you to stop
用紧急呼叫打断你们的好事儿
The miscegenation with an emergency page.
你怎么觉得我们会...
What made you think we'd...
他说你们每早都做
He said you guys do it every morning.
每个人都在撒谎  记得吗
Everybody lies. Remember?
所以你们其实没有...
So you weren't actually...
再见  豪斯
Good-bye, House.
我得在给钱以前得到个确定答案
I'm gonna need a definitive answer before any money changes hands.
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt,
可代表们要求看预算
But the grc called about the budgets,
药房还等着呢
The pharmacy is still waiting,
还有8点30开会的人已经到了
And your 8:30 just arrived on campus.
他10分钟就到了
He should be here in ten minutes.
我敢肯定只有今天他来早了
Figured this would be the one day he comes early.
您能帮我校对一下这个吗
Can you proofread this for me?
你什么时候能找个助理呢
When are you gonna find your own assistant?
今天不行  谢谢你
Not today. Thank you.
我五分钟后回来
I'll be back in five.
卡迪医生
Dr. Cuddy.
我知道通常我们两客户接待处人员
I know we're usually fine with two C.S. Reps,
但以防万一  我今天需要多些帮手
But I want a few extra hands today just in case.
还需要信息部检查一下网络
And have I.T. recheck the network.
我不想一会儿听到新电话线
I don't want to hear later that the new lines
只能打出去  或者电脑崩溃什么的
Can only dial out or the computer crashed.
-怎么样了  -希望没事
- What's going on? - Hopefully nothing.
你准备好接电话就可以了
Just make sure you're ready if people start calling.
-你要见我吗  -卡迪医生
- You wanted to see me? - Hey, Dr. Cuddy.
是的  我想让你知道
Yeah, uh, I wanted to let you know
昨晚下的一个药品订单有点问题
There's a problem with one of the orders that came in last night.
怎么
Which is?
他们送来了两倍的药
They sent double the amount of meds we ordered.
-你打电话问过为什么了吗  -是的
- Did you call and ask why? - Yeah.
他们坚持说不是他们搞错了
They insist it's not a mistake.
那就给当地邮局发传真
So fax them the original P.O.
是的  我本来就是要这么做的
Yeah, that's what I was planning on doing,
但  我找不到
But, um... I can't find it.
实际上  根本找不到他们
Actually, I can't find any of them.
奥斯卡  我没时间看你的材料
Oscar, I don't have time to straighten out your paperwork.
-斯坦在哪  -他9点还没来
- Where's Stan? - He doesn't get in till 9:00
而且那不是我的材料
And it's actually not my paperwork.
是盖尔的  她今天病了
It's Gail's paperwork, and she's out sick today.
那就放在她桌上等她回来搞定它
So put it on her desk and let her figure it out when she comes back.
好的  但不是我的错  如果...
All right, but it's not my problem if...
奥斯卡  今天不行  好吗
Oscar, not today, okay?
是整批货还是只有一种药呢
Was it the whole shipment or just one med?
-只有一种  -维可丁吗
- It's just one. - Vicodin?
不是  是25毫克装的麻黄碱胶囊
No, 25 milligram ephedrine tablets.
什么
What?
给盖尔打电话
Call Gail.
跟她说我要在我办公室尽快见到她
Tell her I want to see her in my office asap.
可她病了
But she's sick.
满世界都是病人
This place is full of sick people.
-让她来  -卡迪医生
- Just get her in here. - Dr. Cuddy,
8点30开会的人都在你办公室等你
Your 8:30 is waiting in your office.
现在
Now.
我马上上楼
Oh, I got to make a quick trip upstairs.
你能给开会的人倒杯咖啡吗
Can you get the guy in my office a cup of coffee?
我马上就来
I'll be right back.
我给你倒过咖啡了
I've gotten you coffee before.
怎么了
What's wrong?
这真冷
It's freezing in here.
冻得我都没知觉了
I can hardly feel my fingers.
求你告诉我你拨打紧急求救电话
Please tell me you didn't send a 911 page
不是只为了告诉我暖气坏了
To tell me the heater's broken.
暖气没坏
It's not broken.
豪斯收买了设备处  开了中央空调
House bribed the physical plant to turn on the ac
所以我得快点
So I'd hurry up.
那就快点
So hurry up.
这个人腹部开了个大口
This man's abdomen is wide open.
他的体温降到华氏95度了
His core temp is down to 95.
好的  我会处理的
Fine. I will deal with it.
你最好快点  要不我就去告...
You better or I'm gonna file...
不管他和你说什么  现在把暖气打开
I don't care what he told you. Turn it back up now.
我以为你要开大会呢
Thought you had an important meeting.
你真是个白痴
You're an idiot.
等下一次你在给病人做肝脏移植手术时 遇到这情况  你会怎么办
What are you gonna do the next time one of your patients needs a liver transplant?
去跟威尔森扯淡吧
Go talk to Wilson about something completely unrelated
看看会是什么结果
And see what happens.
神秘感染的那家伙现在满身长疮了
Mystery infection guy is now covered in boils
而且脓包都有拳头大
And has an abscess big enough to put your fist in.
他必须马上做手术
He needs to get into an O.R. Tout suite.
胡让尼马上就做完了
Hourani will be done soon.
好的
Good.
那我就先去喝杯热巧
I'll have some hot chocolate waiting.
玛丽娜  嘿
Marina, hey.
孩子怎么样了
How's she doing?
她吐了吗
She vomited?
让她吃点布洛芬  再给她洗个澡
Give her some more ibuprofen and put her in the bath for a bit.
半个小时后不见好转再给我打电话
And call me in a half an hour if it doesn't go down.
对不起  玛丽娜
Sorry, Marina.
我得接个电话
I have another call.
半小时后不管怎样就给我电话
Just call me in a half an hour either way.
嘿  怎么了
Hey. What's up?
告诉他  我在路上
Tell him I'm halfway there.
是他非要坚持早上见面的
He's the one who insisted on the early meeting.
我   好的  马上到
I-- all right, I'm coming.
早上好  伊莱
Morning, Eli.
-不好意思让你等了  -没事
- Sorry about the wait. - Oh, it's all right.
听说你孩子病了
I hear you got a sick kid.
我知道那是什么情形
Yeah, I know what that's like.
应该说是我老婆知道
Or I should say my wife does.
那么你们是准备做些让步
So you guys ready to give some ground
然后继续谈生意吗
So we can make this deal?
为什么要我们让步
Why would we do that?
我们已经谈了八个月了
We've been going at this for eight months.
只要你合理一点我们就会很快结束
Soon as you decide to get reasonable.
难道是我说的不合理吗
I'm the one that's unreasonable?
我的每个议案你都要用几周的时间才答复
You've taken weeks to respond to every proposal I've presented.
大西洋保险是新泽西最大的保险提供商
AtlanticNet Insurance is the largest healthcare
你们也不是 唯一合同到期了的医院
Provider in new Jersey, and you're not the only hospital whose contracts are up.
那你们准备好开始谈判了吗
So is your team ready to come back to the table?
不  我们不接受
Yeah. We're not going to.
这是我们的最终报价
This is our final offer.
我们愿意按人数计算
We're willing to go with a capitated structure,
但是我们需要对所有人的赔偿最少上涨12%
But we need at least 12% increase in reimbursements across the board.
好消息是  这次我能很快答复你
Well, the good news is I can give you a quick response.
门都没有
Not a chance.
不管怎么说  和你交谈很愉快
But as always, nice talking to you.
替我向你妹妹问好
Say hi to your sister for me.
如果你不接受这个报价
If you don't accept the offer,
我们就终止合同
We're gonna terminate the contract.
如果你的全部病人都付现金
Gonna be hard to keep this place open
那么这个地方就要关门了
If all your patients have to pay cash.
普林斯顿普雷斯波罗医院是我们公司最小的客户
Princeton plainsboro is the smallest hospital in our entire network.
-我们也是最好的  -也还是一样
- We're also the best. - Doesn't matter.
我们要对1300万的病人负责
We are responsible for covering 13 million people.
我们没钱给他们买跑车
We don't have enough cash to buy them all maseratis.
我知道你是怎么赔付卑尔根医院
I know what you paid Bergen,
纽瓦克贝思以色列  和罗伯特伍德强生医院
Newark Beth Israel, Robert Wood Johnson--
因为他们有优势
'cause they have leverage.
你要么规模小  要么价格高
You can be expensive or small,
不可能两样全占
But you can't be both.
我已经让琼斯柯廷公司处理公关问题了
I've engaged Jones & Curtin to handle the P.R.,
我准备在下午三点 发布声明
And I'm prepared to make the announcement at 3:00 p.M. Today.
每一个最优秀的扑克玩家都知道不能打情绪牌
First lesson every good poker player learns is don't get emotional.
你手上什么牌都没有
You don't have the cards.
你越快意识到这一点
And the sooner you realize that,
我们就能越快达成一个合理的协议
The sooner a reasonable contract will get signed.
下午三点之前你还可以改变主意
You have until 3:00 p.m. to change your mind.
我一直喜欢你的办事风格
I always did like your style.
弄成这样我也不好受
Gonna be sad to see you go.
他们在会议室等你
They're waiting for you in the conference room.
谢谢
Thanks.
把这个拿到呼叫中心
Uh, take this up to the call center
让克劳迪娅发给每个客户接待处人员
And tell Claudia to give one to each C.S. Rep
让他们在每个问题上都要回答
And to start going over the answers to each question.
好的
Okay.
无论发生什么情况都不要让别人知道这件事
And under no circumstances is any of this info to go outside that room.
这些东西是有数的
The scripts are numbered and I want a list
我要一个她发放的名单知道了  还有什么吗
Of every person she gives one to. Got it. Anything else?
没了
No.
你真想要做这桩生意
If you really wanted to make a deal,
你应该摆个俯卧撑的造型
You should have ditched the push-up
最好是做到一半的
And gone with a demi.
男的为了看胸部会不顾一切的
Nothing makes a guy wanna close like high beams.
你听说什么了
What have you heard?
你和一个狡猾家伙的会面了不到五分钟
Your meeting with the weasel lasted less than five minutes,
就是说要么你同意了完全合理地做一个
Which means you either agreed to a completely sensible
30天的合同延期  或者是你们其中某人提出了一个完全荒唐的最终提案
30-day extension or one of you issued a completely ridiculous ultimatum.
太好了  你还是他
Oh, goodie. You or him?
-我  -加油哦  老板
- Me. - Way to go, boss.
你才用了荒唐这个词
You just said it was ridiculous.
做者荒唐  观者有趣
Ridiculous to make. Fun to watch.
只要不是虚张声势
As long as it's not just a bluff.
告诉我不是虚张声势
Please tell me it's not a bluff.
不是虚张声势  也不荒唐
It is not a bluff, and it is not ridiculous.
不过因为我们不是什么巨型医院
Just because we're not some huge--
我们还没让Pluta先生躺好 他就开始出现幻觉了
Mr. Pluta started hallucinating before we could put him under.
血压下降
His B.P. is plummeting.
心跳加快
He has an elevated heart rate.
看起来像充血性心力衰竭
Looks like congestive heart failure.
有意思
Interesting.
我不关心怎么有意思
I don't care how interesting it is.
你不许用疟疾感染他
You are not infecting him with malaria.
什么时候疟疾能治疗心力衰竭了
Since when is malaria a cure for heart failure?
不能
It's not.
不是充血性心力衰竭
It's not congestive heart failure.
应该是
It's gotta be...
刚接到胡让尼的电话
Just got off the phone with Hourani.
对不起  戴夫  我现在真没空
I'm sorry, Dave. I don't really have time right now--
你以为我有时间听他抱怨20分钟
Think I had time to listen to him go for 20 minutes
就说手术室里的温度这点事吗
About the damn temperature in the O.R.?
我处理好了
I took care of it.
不是它
It's not an "it."
你该处理的应该是他
It's a "Him" You need to take care of.
你要所有员工都奉迎豪斯所有的诡异想法  而我甚至
You got the entire staff catering to house's every whim, and I can't get approval
不能雇佣一个外科医生来填补
To hire a replacement for the surgeon
他从我的部门偷走那人的空缺
He stole from my department?
他是我的首席医生
A doctor I only took on in the first place
仅仅是由于你的压力
Because of pressure from you.
就是说你当初不想要奇斯
So you didn't want Chase,
但是现在因为没了他而生气
But now you're pissed you can't have him?
你想召开委员会
You want to convene a search committee
重新找一位外科主任吗
And start looking for a new chief of surgery?
不  戴夫
No, Dave.
那就别总忙着替他收拾残局
Then you better stop spending all your time
先做好你的工作吧
Putting out his fires and start doing your damn job.
托马斯医生那里有问题吗
There a problem with Dr. Thomas?
不  只是一个手术室的小问题
No, just refereeing a dispute about the O.R.
现在我们还没有和大西洋保险签合同
So we don't yet have a contract with Atlanticnet.
我们已经多给了你一周时间
We gave you an extra week
你确定今天会有答复的
And you assured us you'd have a deal by today.
我们可以成交  但与我们期望绝不相符
We could have a deal, just not the deal we deserve.
你想要什么  继续延期吗
So what do you want, approval for an extension?
我们已经讨论这个8个月了
We've been at this for eight months.
继续延期不会改变什么
An extension isn't gonna change anything.
你的计划是什么
So what's your plan?
我提出了最终报价
I presented a final offer.
我说我们愿意按照人数计费
I told them that we would agree to a capitated structure
只要他们把赔偿提高12%
If they increase reimbursements by 12%.
最终报价  什么意思
A final offer? What does that mean?
如果下午三点之前他们不接受
If they don't accept it by 3:00,
我们就终止合作
We're gonna terminate.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
如果我们不跟大西洋保险合作
If we don't accept atlanticnet insurance,
就会丢掉80%的病人
We'll lose 80% of our patients.
能继续开业三个月就是幸运了
We'd be lucky to last three months.
我们没要求他们能力之外的
We're not asking for anything they can't afford.
他们的最终报价是提高4%
Their last offer was a 4% increase
你要求的是12%
And you're demanding 12.
有些地方他们赔得更多
They're paying even more at some places.
有些是入住率还不如我们这里的医院
Units that have lower ratings than ours.
在理论世界中  那说辞还有效
In a perfect world, that would definitely matter.
桑福德  他们只关心利润增长率
Sanford, they're all about growth.
他们也知道如果市场宣传说自己是最大的
And they know they don't get new customers
他们就没有新的客户而言了
By marketing themselves as the biggest.
因此他们一直宣传自己是最好的
They do it by claiming they're the best,
如果他们的病人不再来我们这里就医他们就不能再这样宣传自己了
And they can't do that if their patients can't come to us.
你跟摩根谈的时候他有什么反应
What was Morgan's reaction when you told him?
他没有同意  但他会的
He didn't give in, but he will.
我告诉他3点以前给我答复
I told him I'd make the announcement at 3:00.
他会在3点前给我回电话的
He'll call back before then.
他们需要我们
They need us.
不  是我们需要他们
No, we need them.
我们相互共生
We need each other.
谈判是你的责任
The negotiation is your responsibility,
所以我们没法阻拦你的想法
So we can't stop you if this is what you want to do.
但我们都清楚
But just so we're clear,
如果我们不跟大西洋保险合作的话
If we don't have a contract with atlanticnet,
你也许不会在雇佣我们了
You're not gonna have a contract with us.
猜猜是谁没来门诊值班
Guess who didn't show up for clinic duty?
别告诉我
Oh, don't tell me.
满身长疮的病人需要肝脏移植
The guy with all the boils needs a liver transplant.
不  是他的医生需要休息了
No, his doctor needs a nap.
需要我把他找出来吗
You want me to try to find him?
-你真的需要他吗  -我需要个医生
- You really need him? - I need someone.
我得了癌症
I have cancer.
你为什么觉得自己得了癌症
Why do you think you have cancer?
不是我觉得
I don't think I have cancer.
而是知道我的确得了癌症
I know I have cancer.
六个月前  我做手术摘掉
I had surgery to remove a malignant polyp
结肠中的恶性肿瘤
In my colon six months ago,
现在它已经转移到我的肺部和淋巴了
And now it's spread to my liver and lymph nodes.
就是说你已经被肿瘤科专家确诊了
So you're under the care of an oncologist?
是的 但是他们不给我需要的处方
Yeah, but he won't give me the prescription I need.
你还需要多开点止痛药吗
Do you need more painkillers?
不  我需要母乳
No. I need breast milk.
-人的母乳吗  -是的
- Human breast milk? - Yes.
那里有抗癌成分
It has cancer-fighting qualities.
对于新生儿来说母乳喂养可以降低以后的患癌风险
Well, in newborns, it's been shown to reduce future risk.
不  对患了癌症的成人也一样
No, in adults with cancer too.
我读过相关著作
I've read studies.
你看...
Look...
我甚至知道哪里可以买到人乳
I even know a place where I can buy it.
我只是需要医生开个处方我就可以去买了然后得到保险公司的赔偿
I just need a prescription so I can get reimbursed by my insurance company.
他们承诺可以赔偿母乳 作为癌症治疗的费用吗
They said they'd reimburse the cost of breast milk as a cancer treatment?
他们会赔偿处方药的费用
They reimburse prescriptions,
所以如果你能给我开个处方
So if you write me a prescription,
他们就没别的选择必须给我支付了
Then they have no choice but to pay.
事实上  他们有其他选择
Well, actually, they have a choice.
你是干什么的  保险公司的业务员吗
What are you, some type of shill for the insurance company?
不是
No.
我已经付保险费30年了
Look, I've been paying premiums for 30 years,
我的有生之年却一天都没病过 直到现在得了癌症
And I've never been sick a day in my life till this happened.
现在我没法工作
Now I can't work.
我没有经济来源
I got no money.
现在你却帮他们欺骗我吗
And you want to help them screw me over?
-我没有欺骗你  -那就给我开处方吧
- I'm not screwing you over. - Well, then give me the script.
那帮不了你的
It won't help you.
-会伤害到我吗  -不会 但是...
- Will it hurt me? - No, but--
好吧  就是说伤害不到你我
Okay, so it won't harm me and it won't harm you,
顶多伤害到保险公司而已
But it's this insurance company--
这跟保险没有关系
This is not about insurance.
那就给我开该死的处方吧
Then give me the damn script.
我生病了
I'm sick.
我需要帮助
I need help.
我需要处方
I need something.
对不起
I'm sorry.
婊子
Bitch.
有人打电话吗
Anyone call?
有
Yeah.
急诊室来电话
The E.R.
他们说值班的血管外科没有优先权
They said the vascular who's on call doesn't have privileges.
那他为什么还值班
Then why is he on call?
多德在开会让他来代替了
Dowd's at a conference and got him to fill in.
如果他能找个真能好好工作的人就好
Be nice if he got somebody who can actually work here.
叫艾瑞克夫斯基来替他
Call ereshefsky.
艾瑞克夫斯基吗  她不会来的
Ereshefsky? She's not gonna do it.
她欠我人情  那她也不会来的
She owes me a favor. She's still not gonna do it.
好吧
All right.
有个人在你办公室
Oh, and there's a guy in your office.
-我猜他是个律师  -为什么在我办公室
- I think he's a lawyer. - Why is he in my office?
他说他不想坐在一堆病人中间
Said he didn't want to sit around a bunch of sick people.
我阻止过他
I tried to stop him.
-我是丽莎·卡迪医生  -罗纳尔多·韦斯布鲁克
- I'm Dr. Lisa cuddy. - Ronald westbrook.
感谢你抽时间来会见我
I appreciate your taking the time to meet with me.
没办法  你已经在我办公室里了
Hard to avoid since you're already in my office.
对不起  我生病刚好
Sorry about that, I just got over
一场重感冒  我不想再...
A wicked cold that didn't want to...
需要我帮什么忙吗
How can I help you?
我代表马丁·阿塞韦
I represent martin acevedo.
他对普林斯顿普雷斯波罗医院提起诉讼
He's filed a suit against pph
罗伯特·奇斯医生没经过同意就做了手术
And dr. Robert Chase for performing surgery without consent.
我明白了
Yes, I saw that.
我也看见手术同意书了
I also saw the consent forms.
他们都签字了
They were all signed.
是的  但他却向我的委托人保证
Yes, but my client was assured
整个手术过程就仅仅是做几处小小的缝合
That the procedure would just be a few minor sutures.
等等
Wait.
你的委托人意外地用锯子切断了拇指 对吧
Your client accidentally cut his thumb off with a table saw, right？
是的  奇斯医生把它接上了
Yes. And Dr. Chase reattached it?
对
Yes.
你是说他不想拇指接上吗
You're saying he didn't want it reattached?
对  他的确不想
No, he most certainly did not.
他只得到了保险公司60%住院费用赔偿
His insurance only covered 60% of inpatient expenses,
所以他只同意最便宜的治疗方案
So he would only agree to the cheapest option.
那你怎么跟他说的
So what did you tell him?
我说把露出骨头部分的皮肤缝合
I said I'd sew up the skin over the exposed bone.
然后我让他躺下 在护理人员那拿来他的拇指然后接上了
Then I put him under, got his thumb from the paramedics, and reattached it.
他想干什么  告诉法官
What's he gonna do?
我把他重要的指头接上而伤害到他了吗
Tell the judge that I harmed him by reattaching a vital digit?
他和他的保险公司都起诉了 都不想付手术费用
Both he and the insurance company are suing to get out of paying the bill.
超过8万美金
It's over $80,000.
那是他的拇指
It was his thumb.
我不能就为了剩几个小钱让他把它扔到垃圾堆里
I couldn't just let him toss it in the trash to save a few bucks.
生病的药剂师来了
The pharm tech who called in sick is here.
她在你的办公室里
She's waiting in your office.
他看都不看我一眼
He barely even looks at me anymore.
我们已经几个月没有做爱了
We haven't had sex in months.
你不需要靠吃药减肥
You don't need pills to lose weight.
有更健康的办法  合法途径
There are healthier ways, legal ways.
你不知道那有多难
You don't understand how hard it is.
自从我生了第二个孩子  不管我怎么做
Ever since our second child, no matter what I do.
我只是想减掉10磅甚至更多
I just wanted to lose ten more pounds
我坚持不下去了
And then I was gonna stop.
对不起
I'm sorry.
伪造药物订单  偷窃...
Forging pharmaceutical orders, stealing...
不要解雇我  卡迪医生
Don't fire me, Dr. Cuddy.
求你了  我恳求你
Please. I'm begging you.
如果萨姆发现了  他肯定会和我离婚
If Sam finds out, he'll divorce me for sure,
还有我的孩子们
And my kids
我发誓我下不为例
I will never do it again, I swear.
求求你再给我一次机会
Just give me a second chance.
我不会将偷窃报告给毒品管理局
I won't report the theft to the DEA...
但我不得不解雇你
But I have to fire you.
花点时间让自己平静一下吧
Just take a few minutes to compose yourself,
我去找人力资源部  给你最后的支票
Then go down to hr and they'll give you your last check.
我这7年来一直都是最优秀的员工
I've been a perfect employee for seven years.
我明白  但是这事闹得太大
I know, but this is too big.
对不起
I'm sorry.
今天怎么样
How's it going?
要在三个小时内把医院从破产中解救出来
Got three hours to save this place from bankruptcy,
刚刚解雇了一名我们的优秀员工
I just fired one of my best employees,
而且照看我那生病孩子的保姆不回我电话
and the woman taking care of my sick child isn't returning my calls.
瑞秋会没事儿的
Rachel's gonna be fine,
不管那位员工是男是女  开除一定有理
I'm sure whoever he or she is deserved it,
最后  我们不会破产的
And we're not going bankrupt.
-真不会吧  -别担心
- Are we?  - Don't worry.
董事会在医院破产之前会先开除我
The board will fire me before they allow that to happen.
他们绝对不会开除你的
They'd never fire you.
我刚刚告诉大西洋保险 如果不给我们12%的提升我将终止合同
I just told Atlanticnet Insurance I'd terminate unless they gave us a 12% bump.
他们有可能开除你了
They might fire you.
玛丽娜  是我
Marina, hey, it's me.
我没有收到你的回信儿
I haven't heard back from you.
你能尽快给我回个电话吗
Can you call me as soon as you can?
谢了
Thank you.
你没试试找卢卡斯吗
You try Lucas?
他不是在睡觉就是在躲着我
He's either sleeping or avoiding me.
你们吵架了吗
You in a fight?
还没有  但是快了
Not yet, but we're gonna be.
你觉得我应该怎样应对大西洋保险呢
What do you think I should do about Atlanticnet?
你正在咨询一个
You're asking a guy who paid
曾经花正价买新车的人
full sticker price for his last car.
你问过豪斯吗
You ask House?
他是个操纵人心的大师总是能得到他想要的
He's a master manipulator who always gets what he wants.
现在的局势已经够失控了
This situation is out of control enough already.
我最不希望的就是豪斯也被卷进来
House is the last person I want to get involved.
从我的椅子上起开
Get out of my chair.
你问的事情还是不行
And the answer is no.
你知不知道有多少 黄色网站的域名里含有妈妈的字样
You ever noticed how many porn sites have "Mom" in the domain name?
辣妈网  饥渴妈妈网  熟妈网
Hot moms, hungry moms, mature moms.
这些应该让你感觉良好的
That ought to make you feel pretty good.
你想要什么
What do you want?
貌似高烧  强烈情绪波动
Looks like boils, altered mental status,
还有心脏衰竭都是由肾细胞癌引起的
and heart failure was called by renal cell carcinoma.
我需要你签字批准让我用疟疾病来治疗它
I need your signature to start treating it with malaria.
别担心
Don't worry.
我同时给他化疗了
I'm giving him chemo too.
是什么让你突然对疟疾痴心绝对呢
What is your sudden obsession with malaria?
只是想履行我那削减开支的部分
Just trying to play my part cutting costs.
疟疾病是消除低体温症状
Malaria is the simplest, cheapest method
最简单  最便宜的方法了
of delivering hypothermia.
是这样
Right.
你需要唯一需要关心的金钱是
The only money you care about...
你是不是跟谁打赌了说你能用疟疾作为一种诊断工具
You bet someone you could use malaria as a diagnostic tool?
那可真不像是我做的事情啊
That doesn't sound like me.
当我没说
Forget it.
好吧  跟你直说了  让一个病人
Okay, let me see if I've got this straight.
处于微小风险的打赌算得上无理取闹吗
A bet that puts one patient at minor risk is juvenile?
而且是不负责任和危险的
And irresponsible and dangerous.
回到大局  在对抗大西洋保险的战争中
But going all in against atlanticnet--
那可不是在打赌
Is not a bet.
那是一场精心策划的谈判
That is a carefully considered negotiating position.
我把这个放进你的收信箱里了
I'm gonna put this in your inbox.
希望你别弄丢了
I just hope it doesn't get lost
相信经历过所有这些以后你会仔细考虑的
Underneath all the other stuff you're carefully considering.
能帮我看一下这些日程表吗
Can you take a look at these per diem schedules?
如果有时间冲突通知我
Let me know if you see any conflicts.
明白
Got it.
对了  艾瑞克夫斯基的确来过
Oh, and Ereshefsky actually did come in.
你抓到她把海绵落在病人身上了吗
You catch her leaving a sponge in a guy or something?
-并不是医学过失  -那是因为什么
- Wasn't a medical mistake. - What was it?
现在不能告诉你了  因为她来过
Can't tell you now. She came in.
嘿  斯坦
Hey, Stan!
黄麻素的订单你核查了没有
Have you audited the ephedrine orders yet?
为什么要查  你告诉我她已经承认了
Why? You told me she confessed.
-斯坦  -行了  好吧
- Stan. - All right, yeah.
-我会处理的  -今天就查
- I'll take care of it. - Today.
你知道他现在正对你骂骂咧咧呢
You know he's cussing you out in there now.
只要他能核查  我无所谓
I don't care as long as he does it.
-真是个贱人  -你来这儿干嘛
- What a bitch. - What are you doing here?
听说你忙得顾不上午餐
Sounded like you were going to be too busy for lunch,
所以这是我的拿手菜  菠菜烤宽面
so my specialty, spinach lasagna.
你确定不是来找其他的人
Sure you didn't come looking for more people
把咱们的性生活吹嘘吗
You could brag about our sex life too?
好吧  抱歉
Okay. Sorry.
从现在开始  关于咱们的性生活
From now on, I got nothing but bad things
我会只捡不好的方面说
to say about our sex life.
或者什么都不说
Or nothing to say.
玛丽娜是怎么回事呢
And what's going on with Marina?
-她不回我电话  -她本来要回电来的
- She hasn't called me back. - She was gonna call.
我告诉她我会告诉你一切都好的
I told her I'd let you know everything was okay.
那么说她的烧退了
So her fever broke?
如果烧退了  那么又意味着什么呢
What exactly does that mean, "When a fever breaks"?
卢卡斯  我非常的忙
Lucas, I'm very busy.
她到底发烧了还是没发烧
Does she have a fever or not?
这是你的午饭
That was gonna be your lunch?
而且你也没吃早饭
And you didn't have breakfast either.
不  她不发烧了
No, she doesn't have a fever,
而且疹子  看起来就像是小尿疹
And the rash was just, like, a little diaper rash.
什么疹子  她起疹子了吗
What rash? She has a rash?
小疹子
Little one.
丽莎  别担心  我正跟你说呢
Lisa, don't worry. I'm telling you.
哦  天啊
Oh, god.
我一定是错拿了玛丽娜的手机
I must have grabbed Marina's cell by mistake.
而且为了睡个好觉
And I turned the ringer off on the home phone
我把家里的电话调静音了
so I could sleep.
你想对我怎么着
What are you doing to me?
我猜你的谈判还没结束呢
I take it your deal's not done.
暂时还没有
Not yet.
不如让我去查一查那个负责谈判的家伙的老底怎么样
How about I take a quick look into the guy who's in charge of the negotiations?
或者直接查CEO的就更好了
Or better yet, the CEO.
如果查到他们的污点  你可以当成把柄
If I get some dirt, you can use it as leverage.
时间不够了
There's no time.
你是怎么找到那些家伙的呢
How do you even find these guys?
谢谢
Thanks.
你应该见过那家伙当时的表情
You should have seen the guy's face.
我当时还以为他脸上
I thought he was gonna have a damn coronary
长出来一个冠状瘤呢
right there in the tee box.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你是基思·泰尼鲍姆
You're Keith Tannenbaum,
大西洋保险的CEO对吧
Ceo of Atlanticnet Insurance, right?
是我  我能为你做点什么呢
That's me. How can I help you?
事实上我觉等我们可以互相帮助
Well, actually, I think we can help each other.
我是丽莎·卡迪医生
I am Dr. Lisa Buddy,
普林斯顿普雷斯波罗教学医院的院长
Dean of medicine at Princeton Plainsboro.
哦  是啊  你好吗
Oh, yeah. Well, how are you?
我有一点儿小小的不开心
Well, I'm a little unhappy.
你也知道了我们医院和贵公司的合同
You're aware that our contract
将于这个礼拜到期
with your company is up this week?
是的  我们组建了一个谈判小组他们正在处理这些
Yes, and we have a negotiating team that's working all that out.
普林斯顿普雷斯波罗教学医院拥有全国
Princeton Plainsboro has the highest-rated E.R.
最高级别急诊室  最先进的重症监护室
in the state, the most advanced ICU,
和整个国家里最创新的诊断学医疗科室
and the most innovative diagnostic medicine department in the entire country.
很高兴了解这些
Good to know.
现在如果您不介意的话我要
Now if you don't mind, I'd like to--
而大西洋保险公司的营销预算
While Atlanticnet Insurance has a marketing budget
比我们的儿科重症监护室
That's more than our pediatric ICUs
和器官移植科室加起来还多
and transplant units combined.
你们的职业高尔夫球巡回赛赞助 就足够支付我们免费诊所的开销了
Your PGA sponsorship could pay for our walk-in clinic,
而你那两架私人飞机的燃料费
And the money you spend to fuel your two private jets
足够支付我们空中救护服务达三年之久
could fund our air ambulance service for the next three years.
-你的论点是  -你们公司的利润增长
- Your point being? - Your growth may be good
或许对你自己腰包扩充有利
for your bottom line,
但对我们来说能去拯救生命
but ours allows us to save lives.
所以我宁愿不选择向媒体宣布
And I would rather not have to announce to the press
你们公司要节约成本时
how selective your company appears to be
所展现出来的选择性倾向
When it comes to cutting costs.
摩根说得对
Well, Morgan was right.
你是个强硬的家伙 你可以把我描绘成一个富有的混蛋
You are one tough gal. You can portray me as a rich bastard
媒体那边随你怎么说
In the press all you want,
只要我依然富有
just as long as I stay rich.
-斯坦在找你  -我很忙
- Stan is looking for you. - I'm busy.
他说是非常紧急的事
He said it's urgent.
我不明白  这怎么可能
I don't understand how it's even possible.
我检查了两次
I've checked it twice.
-多少  -10箱
- How much?  - Ten cases.
-10箱  -三年前就开始了
- Ten cases? - Going back three years.
你到底在干嘛  斯坦
What the hell have you been doing, Stan?
你应该是来管理这儿呢
You're supposed to be managing this place.
我签署的文件都是对的
All the paperwork I signed was correct.
她肯定是之后改了订单
She must have altered the orders afterwards.
订单来了后你没再交叉核对过吗
Didn't you ever cross-check it with the bills that came in?
我交给别人做了
I delegated it.
给谁
To whom?
盖尔
To Gail.
她看上去很可靠
Look, she seemed perfectly trustworthy.
我怎么会知道
How was I supposed to know?
-做好你的工作你就知道了  -抱歉
- By doing your job. - I'm sorry.
你通知毒品管制所了吗
Have you notified the DEA?
-毒品管理局  -天啊斯坦  拜托
- The DEA? - Jeez, Stan. Hello!
才不会有人偷5万英镑的药
You don't steal $50,000 worth of pills
用来减肥呢
because you want to lose weight.
她在为制造毒品提供原料
She's supplying a meth lab.
赶紧把她叫回来
Just get her back in here.
好的
All right.
马上
Now.
如果你想找工作  相信我
Oh, you ever want a job, trust me.
他会给你双倍的工资
He'll double whatever you're making here.
看来他喜欢我的提议
Take it he liked my proposal.
喜欢到要我厚着脸皮又过来一趟
Enough to tell me to get my ass back over here today.
给你
Here.
他愿意增加到8%
He's willing to go to 8%.
-8  -我们之前可是4
- Eight? - We were at four.
董事会肯定会觉得你已经很了不起了
Your board's gonna think you walk on water.
我就要12  否则免谈
I want 12.
你不可能拿到12的
You're not gonna get 12.
那是痴人说梦
There's just no way.
8%才勉强负担了我们的成本膨胀
8% barely covers our cost inflation.
但按人数计算可以让你降低成本膨胀
But capitated structure should allow you to hold down inflation.
而且把你们的风险都转给了我们
And shifts all your risk onto us,
所以12是我们应得的
which is why we deserve 12.
丽莎  得了吧
Lisa, come on.
给我修草坪的人比我孩子的老师还赚得多
The guy who mows my lawn makes more than my kid's teacher.
那两个午饭时间被你打扰的人
Hell, the two guys whose lunch you interrupted
他们可能被开除  解雇费估计
could get fired, and their severance would be more
比他们多数员工一生赚的钱还要多
than most of their employees make in a lifetime.
早就不是一分耕耘一分收获的年代了
It doesn't have anything to do with what you deserve.
就这样了
This is it.
要么照单全收  要么一文不取
Take it or leave it.
你在干嘛呢
What are you doing?
你知道什么优秀的移植外科医生吗
Know any good transplant surgeons?
原来他除了肾脏  还有其他的器官衰竭
Turns out his kidneys aren't the only thing failing.
我知道你在想什么
And I know what you're thinking.
疟疾不会那么快就毁了他的肝
But malaria wouldn't destroy his liver that fast,
更何况我们根本没用疟疾
especially since we never infected him.
你不是说
I thought you said--
显然  福曼觉得他翅膀够硬了
Apparently Foreman now thinks that he has
以食品及药物管理局不批准为由
the authority to overrule my orders
违抗我的命令
Just because the FDA wouldn't approve.
不用担心  我会搞定他
Don't worry. I'll deal with him.
如果你能和胡让尼谈谈
If you could just talk to Hourani...
你会怎么做
What would you do?
如果你在我做爱的时候呼我
If you paged me during sex?
和大西洋保险公司的合同
About the contract with Atlanticnet.
我让他们提高到8%了
I got them to come up to 8%,
但我们至少得拿到12%
but we should get at least 12.
全是数字游戏 做做算术题就知道了
It's all numbers. Do the math and nothing else.
这不是我的面子问题
It's not about my pride.
而是原则问题
It's about the principle.
他们就是欺负我们规模小
They're trying to screw us over because we're small.
他们不就是干这个的吗
That's what they're supposed to do.
他们该强迫其他医院向我们学习
They should be pressuring other hospitals to be more like us,
而不是倒着来
not trying to make us more like them.
太愚蠢了
It's stupid.
拿你的工作冒险去指出他们的愚蠢不是也很蠢吗
Putting your job on the line in an effort to stamp out stupidity isn't?
你也会这么做
You would.
有可能
Probably.
但我也会为了赢50块
But then I also wanted to try to cure cancer
用感染疟疾去治疗癌症
by infecting a guy with malaria to win a $50 bet.
你真想向我学习吗
You really want to be like me?
大家都知道  过去八个月以来
As you know, for the past eight months,
我们都在和大西洋保险公司
We've been trying to renegotiate our contract
为合同进行谈判
with Atlanticnet Insurance.
过程很艰难重重
It's been a difficult process,
但在下午五点 正式通知出来之前
but I wanted to let you all know before we made the formal announcement
我想先告诉大家
that as of 5:00 P.M. Today,
我们即将终止与大西洋保险公司的合同
our contract with atlanticnet will be terminated.
我们已向客户接待处的呼叫中心
We've doubled the number of customer service representatives
调配了双倍人手
in our call center.
我们将向现有的病人再提供30天的看护
Current patients will still be allowed to remain in our care for 30 days,
但从明天开始 我们将不再接受
But starting tomorrow, we will no longer be accepting patients
享受大西洋保险公司服务的病人
with atlanticnet health insurance.
拜托  玛丽娜
Come on, Marina.
快接电话
Pick up the phone.
忙着呢
I'm busy.
-我们找到匹配的肝脏了  -行
- We found a liver match. - All right.
让他做术前准备吧
Get him prepped.
我会搞定胡让尼的
I'll straighten things out with Hourani.
胡让尼不是问题
Hourani's not the problem.
豪斯才是
House is.
他想让奇斯做手术
Now he wants Chase to do the surgery.
向胡让尼表明他不需要他吗
To prove to Hourani he doesn't need him?
向托马斯证明奇斯才是 外科最厉害的医生
To prove to Thomas that Chase was his department's best surgeon.
奇斯怎么想
And what does Chase want to do?
他想做这个手术
Chase wants to do the surgery.
你不希望他做  是因为
And you don't want him to do it because?
-我不管谁做  -那问题是
- I don't care who does it. - So what's the problem?
为了让病人进手术室
In order to get our patient into the OR,
我们得把他放到手术名单上
we have to get him on the surgery schedule.
而做这件事情  需要一个
In order to do that, we need someone to put him there
豪斯和托马斯都管不了的人
who neither House nor Thomas can overrule.
什么
What?
你难道希望我重新回归维柯丁的怀抱吗
Would you rather I go back on vicodin?
她又不在给你的腿按摩
She's not massaging your leg.
她终究  会的
She will...eventually.
为什么只有我一个人担心这家医院的死活
Why am I the only person here who cares what happens to this hospital?
勤快点  管好你的部门
Get off your ass and get your department under control.
至少这几天帮帮忙
At least for the next few days.
让大西洋保险这种大公司
Gonna take longer than a few days for a company
向你的公关活动低头
the size of Atlanticnet to start feeling
可不是几天的事
the squeeze of your P.R. Campaign.
如果他们会低头的话
If they ever do.
你怎么知道的
And you know this how?
从你一直在研究他们还有他们其他的合同
From all the time you've spent researching them and their other contracts?
他们处理媒体关系的方式吗
The way they handle their press relations?
我知道他们有个纳斯卡车队
I know they have a NASCAR team.
不管你在希伯来学校  或是跟
Despite what you may have learned at Hebrew school
吉米·克里夫(牙买加雷鬼歌手) 学了些什么
or from Jimmy Cliff,
他们越强大
Sometimes the bigger they are,
反击就越厉害
the harder they kick your ass.
我不是贪心
I'm not trying to be greedy.
但他也不希望被医疗费用逼得破产
But he's also not interested in being forced into a medical bankruptcy.
阿塞维多先生  很抱歉你有经济问题
Mr. Acevedo, I am sorry you're having financial difficulties.
但多亏我们  你保住了大拇指
But because of us, you still have a thumb.
我以为一个木匠应该需要大拇指吧
I assume that's something a carpenter might need.
我也以为你见我们
And I assume you didn't ask for this meeting
不是为了教育我的客户吧
so you could lecture my client.
你有保险
You have insurance.
但凭这个诉讼
But by filing this suit,
他们可能拒绝赔付
you've caused us to get paid nothing by them either.
-这跟我们无关  -实际上有关系
- That's not our problem. - Actually it is,
因为他要对我们尚未赔付的费用负责
Since he's responsible for any expense we're not reimbursed.
但是如果你撤诉
But if you drop this suit
并且指明蔡斯医生在为你
And make it clear that Dr. Chase was acting
接断指时是为你着想的
In your best interest when he reattached your thumb,
我们会重新提交索赔请求
Then we'll be able to resubmit the claim.
你们也会支付免赔额
And you'll cover his deductible,
律师费  还有五万元的精神补偿
Attorney's fees, and 50 grand for pain and suffering?
其实  我想说的是我们会替他付免赔额的一半
Actually, I was thinking more like we'd cover half his deductible,
你只要付16000元
Which means you'd only owe $16,000.
你是让他付钱给你
You mean you want him to pay you?
对
Yes.
你知道这手术要花费多少吗
Do you have any idea how much it costs?
培训一名显微外科医生要多少年
How many years it takes to train someone in microsurgery?
我们让你的生活重新步入正轨
We gave you back your life.
你仍然能工作
You can still work.
可以自己系扣子  拿叉子
You can button your own shirt, hold a fork.
马丁  我们走
Martin, let's go.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道自己应该付钱
I know I should pay.
但我不能
But I just can't.
我还是不能正常工作
I still cannot work.
我已经待业在家
I'm already underwater on my house.
还有两个孩子要养
And I have two kids with braces.
你觉得自己少个手指会一切正常
You think you'd be in better shape without a thumb?
目前
Right now...
经济角度看来  是的
Financially? Yeah.
我的确是
I would be.
好吧  我们奉陪
Well, so would we.
你进来时  我们没有这种想法
But when you came in, we didn't think about that,
只是一心为你好
We just took care of you.
竭尽所能让你康复
Made sure we did whatever you needed to get well.
没错  你的医生一心治病救人
Yeah, right, all you doctors care about is healing.
所以停车场里全是
That's why there's all those BMWs and Porsches
-宝马和保时捷  -该死
- In the parking lot. - Damn it.
起来  我们走吧
Come on, we're out of here.
法庭上见
We'll see you in court.
好的  到时见
You're right, you will.
我们为你保住一根手指
You still have a thumb because of us.
同时告诉你
And like everyone else in this world,
天下没有免费的午餐
We don't work for free.
我们靠这份营生赚钱
We earn this money.
即使手术费要你卖掉房子来还
And if we have to take your house to get it,
我们也会收的
We will.
怎么回事
What's going on?
好像有人在打架
I think they're fighting.
让开  都让开
Out of my way, now. Out of my way.
这是怎么一回事
What the hell is going on?
我让他们畅所欲言
I told them to use their words.
那个药剂师回来了
That pharm tech is back.
在你办公室里
She's in your office.
你站那边  你到另一半去
You, there. You, over there.
回到这里之前 我不想听你俩解释
I don't wanna hear a word out of either one of you until I get back.
-你说谎  -那又怎样
- You lied. - So?
你能拿我怎么样
What're you gonna do about it?
首先  向毒品管理局上报
Well, for one... notify the DEA.
很好
Good.
他们肯定对豪斯医生如何强迫我为他偷药
I'm sure they'll be very interested to hear How doctor house forced me to help him steal the meds
同时与他有染的医院行政人员
And the administrator who he's having sex with
如何掩饰这些感兴趣
Has been helping him cover it up.
你真以为自己能瞒天过海吗
You really think you can lie your way out of this?
没错
Yeah, I do.
还想知道什么  贱人
Anything else you wanna know...bitch?
董事局主席想跟你谈谈
The hospital board's chairman wants to speak to you.
- 告诉他我很忙  - 我说了  但是他
-Tell him I'm busy. -I did, but he--
告诉他我不干了
Tell him I quit.
你打赌输给卢卡斯了
You owe lucas the money.
打电话时我们在做爱
We were having sex when you called.
母乳男最终找到愿意
The breast milk guy finally found a doctor
替他开药的医生了
To give him what he wanted.
如果这样能管用  比按照疟疾治疗好
If it works, it's way better than malaria.
值得一试
It was worth a shot.
我
I...
以为他们只是在虚张声势
I thought they were the ones bluffing.
没理由他们任我们终止合同
No way they'd let us terminate.
董事会不会开了你
They're not gonna fire you.
你也不会辞职
And you're not gonna quit.
为什么
Why not?
因为你是个笨蛋
Because you're an idiot.
而这个地方需要你
This place needs you.
这些对你很重要
And that matters to you.
你怎么看那个药剂师
What do you think of that pharm tech?
盖尔
Gail.
是个反社会分子
She's a sociopath.
你知道她偷药
You knew she was stealing meds?
不知道
No.
不过她打开信的样子真怪
But have you seen the way she opens the mail?
怎么你从没告诉过我
Why didn't you ever tell me?
也许这消息有一天能派上用场
Figured it might come in handy one day.
盖尔  我一直欣赏你
Gail, I like you.
一直如此
I always have.
我也知道你不会在不属于你的优势下得偿所愿
And I know you must've gotten sucked up into a situation you weren't able to control.
真的  那你和豪斯就可以胡作非为
Really, is that what happened with you and house?
我不会因为你威胁来诋毁
I'm not gonna back down
就做出让步
Just because you threaten to smear me.
如果你愿意说出事实
Now, if you agree to tell the truth,
我仍然会帮助你
There are things I can do to help.
想想你的丈夫  你的孩子们
Think about your husband, your kids.
我相信你内心还是个好人
I know you're a good person deep down inside.
七年间你做的的一切是不可能瞒过去的
You can't completely hide everything about yourself in seven years.
你可真够傻的
You're an idiot.
上班六个月后我就开始偷了
I started stealing from here six months after you hired me.
到现在你也不怎么了解
You still don't even know the half of it,
而且你永远也不会清楚的
And you never will.
要不是我生了病 这一切还是神不知鬼不觉
You wouldn't have even found out about this if I hadn't gotten sick.
你也没自我感觉那么强硬
And you aren't as tough as you think you are.
你没有勇气炒了我
There's no way you'd let this job get taken away.
因为如果你这么做了
And if I go down...
我会拖你一起下水
You're going down.
斯坦过来时  请把这个交给他
Can you tell stan to give this to
让他上报毒品管理局
The dea agent when he comes by.
一朵花
A flower?
没错  卢卡斯送我的
Yeah, Lucas gave it to me.
也许有一天能派上用场
I thought he might come in handy one day.
上班六个月后
I started stealing from here
我就开始偷了
Six months after you hired me.
太棒了
Nice.
至少有件事能扬眉吐气一次
Least I came out on top once today.
你去哪
Where you going?
把辞呈交给董事会
To hand the board my resignation.
希望无论谁来代替我 都仍能得到那8%
Hopefully whoever they hire to replace me can still get the 8%.
玛丽娜
Marina!
我一整天都在找你
I've been trying to get in touch with you all day.
没事的  我理解
All right, I understand.
瑞秋怎么样
Just how is Rachel?
那疹子呢
And the rash?
太好了
Great.
我会早点回家
I'll be home early--oh!
太好了
Perfect.
你个贱人
You bitch.
没想到你真这么做了
I didn't think you'd actually do it.
告诉你我一定会的
I told you I would.
取消警戒吧
Call the dogs off.
就按你说的12%
You got your 12.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
好啊
Yes!
太棒了
你要接吗？
You gonna get that?